本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
牙套  牙套卡进纱门里啦
Braces, braces caught in the screen door!
谁来记录一下我的遗嘱
Someone dictate my will!
我将把全部财产留给摇摇
I'm giving it all to Waddles!
说"啊"  女汉子
Say "Ah," Girl-dude.
苏斯  你救了我
Soos! You saved me!
这就是我的工作呀  杂耍演员
Just doing my job, hambone!
各位  明天见啦
I'll see you dudes tomorrow!
拜拜  苏斯
Bye, Soos!
晚安  苏斯
Night, Soos!
走向我的车
Walking to my car...
你有没有想过苏斯在
You ever wonder what Soos
离开神秘小屋以后都会干些什么
does when he's not here at the Mystery Shack?
没
No.
没想过
Not really.
一次都没想过
Not once ever.
揍
Punch!
揍扁这些豹子
Punch those leopards.
浅色染发结束了
Ooh, highlights are done!
你将会成为宾果游戏厅里
You are gonna make the
所有老奶奶们嫉妒的对象
other grandmas at the bingo hall so jealous.
稍等一下  我的孩子
Just a minute, mi hijo.
看看这个
Look at this.
你的堂哥瑞吉打算
Your cousin Reggie is having
请参加我们的婚礼
下个月开一个订婚派对
an engagement party next month.
等等  等等  瑞吉订婚了
Wait, wait. Reggie is engaged?
但是他是穷鬼版的苏斯啊
But he's like the poor man's Soos!
我不想给你太大压力
I do not want to pressure you,
但是你也是个男子汉了
but you are a man now.
不管怎么样  你也该约约女孩子了
In a way, it's time for you to start meeting girls.
我还想在看到你生活安定的样子后
I would like to see you settled
再升向天堂和天使们相聚呢
before I ascend to heaven and live with the angels.
也和爷爷相聚
And with grandpa!
不  他不在天堂
No, he is not there.
请你带个姑娘去参加瑞吉的订婚派对吧
Please find a girl to bring to Reggie's engagement.
就算是为了奶奶
Por Abuelita.
当然没问题
No problem!
我最擅长修理东西  打电玩
I'm great at fixing stuff, playing video games,
留小胡子之类的事情
having a sort-of moustache.
我一周之内就能约到女孩的
I could totally get a date in a week.
绝对可以
Totally.
小菜一碟
Piece of cake.
你完蛋了
You're dead.
我完蛋了
I'm dead.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
时间轴： WaitinZ
翻译： violin1443  阿拱  moonywen
■
校订  后期： Enpistu  WaitinZ
怪诞小镇  第二季第五集
Gravity Falls  S02E05  Soos and the Real Girl
你好
Hello!
拜托  别让我糟糕又年迈的脸吓到你
Please, don't let my horrible, elderly face frighten you!
你难道不想用五分钱
Don't you want to use
从金老头那里换些金块吗
that nickel to get a nugget from Old Goldie?
瞧好喽
Watch this!
好吧  说真的  派恩斯先生
Okay, seriously, Mr. Pines,
这东西该丢掉了
it's time to throw that thing out.
它的脸总让人想起那难以抗拒的死亡
Its face reminds everyone of the inevitability of death.
什么
What?
没错  他的表面是有点生锈了
Sure, he's a little rusty around the edges,
但金老头和我一样是经典压轴演员
but Old Goldie's a classic show-stopper like me!
喔  给我松口
Oh, kill it!
快松口啊啊
Kill it!
哈  一个女人
Huh, a woman!
好了  苏斯  你可以的
All right, Soos, you could do this.
只要用你的嘴说出让恋情萌发的话
Just use your mouth to say words that makes romance happen.
你的脸真是好
Your face is good.
在下名为苏斯
I'm a Soos!
苏斯
Soos?
刚才那是怎么回事啊
What was that all about?
我  我觉着我是在调情啊
I-- I think I was flirting!
我也不太确定
But I'm not sure.
有人说"调情"吗
Did someone say flirting?
我算是答应了奶奶
Well, I sort of promised my grandma
在这周之内约到女朋友
I'd get a date by the end of the week.
但是我之前从来没有约过会啊
But I've never actually been on a date before.
故障标  你应该贴在我身上
You belong on me, Out of Order sign.
已坏
终于  上天终于回应了我
Finally, my prayers for a chance
在这个夏天当媒婆的祈求
to match-make this summer have been answered!
苏斯  我的小建议是你得有钱
Soos, a little advice you need to get rich.
或者骗别人说你有钱
Or lie about being rich.
如果不这样  我觉得你也没啥希望了
Outside of that, I don't like your chances.
别听斯坦瞎说  哥们儿
Don't listen to Stan, dude.
你是个开皮卡  有稳定工作的好男人
You're a sweet guy with a steady job and a pickup truck.
你会愿意和他约会吗
Would you date him?
诶哟  你那什么
Oh... would you...
快看那个
Huh, look at that...
苏斯  你帮了我们这么多忙
Soos, you help us so much,
是时候让我们还你个人情了
it's time we help you, dude.
我们一定帮你约到女孩
We're gonna get you that date.
我们会带你去一个
We're taking you where romance lives
浪漫永存  时尚不复的地方
and fashion styles die.
去商业街
To the mall!
我得去找个东西代替金老头
I'm gonna go find a replacement for Old Goldie.
在我走的时候看护好小苏斯
Babysit Soos while I'm gone.
好的  苏斯
All right, Soos,
准备好向这些浑然不觉的女士
are you ready to explode a
引爆你的魅力炸弹了吗
charm bomb on these poor, unsuspecting ladies?
如果我又出糗了怎么办啊
Ah, but what if I embarrass myself again?
放心吧  这种事再糗你也糗不过迪普
Ah, you can't be any worse at this than Dipper.
就是的
Yeah!
等等  你说啥
Wait... what?
预备  调情
And flirt!
眼神接触
Eye contact!
你好呀
Hey there!
我完全不会被你的眼睛吓到的
I'm not scared of your eyes at all!
我会盯着你的眼睛
I'm gonna look at them!
眼神接触
Eye contact.
语言交流
Conversation!
其实吧  我在一头猪的身体里待过
You know I've actually been in a pig's body.
你知不知道猪退着走很累啊
Did you know pigs have a hard time walking backwards?
你当然不会累了
Not you though!
我可没说你是猪
Not that I'm calling you a pig.
你去哪儿啊
Where are you going?
相信自己
Confidence!
那你八成是个女孩  对吧
So you're probably a girl, right?
不对吗
Wrong?
不  我一开始猜对了
No, I was right the first time.
不对吗
Wrong?
往垃圾箱里扔垃圾
Tossing away garbage in the garbage can.
啊  别那么看着我
Ah, don't look at me like that!
有些事就是天注定
This is how it's got to be!
怎么回事
What in the--
这是什么鬼地方
What is this living nightmare?
为什么小孩子这么着迷
Why do kids love it so much?
谁想和喜獾先生一起玩啊
Who wants to get badgered?
没错  那就是"威利・喜獾"
Oh, yeah, that's Will E. Badger.
他专门给吼哈餐厅狂欢会表演
He opens for Hoo-Ha and the Jamboree.
那是威利・喜獾
It's Will E. Badger.
我爱你  威利
I love you, Will E.
现在  把你的钱都给我
Now, give me your money!
拿走我的钱吧  全拿走吧
Take my money! Take it all!
先生  我想买下那个獾
Sir, I would like to buy that badger.
你可玩不动这个  老爷子
You're in over your head, Gramps!
电玩是年轻人的游戏
Animatronics is a young man's game!
披萨机器人老板的硬派生活你肯定扛不住
You couldn't handle the hardcore life of the pizza robot manager.
退缩吧
Flinched!
嗨  你  吐在球池里那个
Hey, you, barfing in the ball pit,
盖瑞这就来
Gary's on the case!
我一定要搞到那只獾
I'm gonna get that badger!
别担心  苏斯
Don't worry, Soos.
我们会找到你的真命天女
You will find the right girl,
你只要"粘"持下去就好
you just need to stick with it.
今天还能再糟糕点吗
Ah, could this day get any worse?
喔  不  堂哥瑞吉
Oh, no, cousin Reggie!
摸摸看  这就是肌肉
Feel it, it's muscle.
不能让他看到这样的我
He can't see me like this!
我必须藏起来
I got to hide!
认命吧  苏斯
This is it, Soos.
注定孤独的一生
A lifetime of loneliness.
只有你们才最爱我
You're the only ones who could love me...
战斗猪猪  迷你光盘版拳头脸医生
Fighty Hogg, Dr. Punch Head MD.
我以前从来没见过这个
Never seen that one before.
"模拟提升你的约会技巧"
"Virtually improve your dating skills,
"十个宅男九个赞"
9 out of 10 basement dwellers recommend!"
这个太棒了
This is perfect!
你打游戏确实比调情厉害多了
Well, I guess you are better at games than at flirting.
能让你约会就怎样都行  苏斯
Anything to get you out there, Soos!
我不确定你是否真的要买那款游戏  先生
I'm not sure you want to buy that game, sir.
这已经是它第三次被退回来了
This is the third time someone's brought that back.
还有字条留言让不惜一切代价毁灭它
And there's a note on it that says destroy at all costs.
嗨  你好啊  你干什么呢
So, hey, there. What's your deal?
就像是  喔她死了
Like the-- Oh, she's dead.
我们放手一搏吧
We'll take our chances.
2000年电子
我真是太期待2000年了
Man, I can't wait for the year 2000.
浪漫学院7
开始
Start!
当魔幻浪漫学园的樱花漫舞之时
"当魔幻浪漫学园的樱花漫舞之时"
When the cherry petals of magic romance academy are in bloom...
婶磨事都可能发僧呦
"婶磨事都可能发僧呦"
anthyding can hadplen.
说得太对了
That is so true.
喔  你好啊
Oh, hi there.
我的名字是姬法妮
My name is Giffany,
我是大学学校里的女学生
I'm a school girl at school university,
你愿意帮我拿下书吗
<i>will you help me carry my books?</i>
没问题！
等不及了！快约会吧！
看！章鱼啊！
我真心觉得该选第二个
I'm really feeling number two here.
点击
Click!
啊  我搞砸了
Ah. I messed up.
没关系
<i>That's okay.</i>
再选一次
<i>Try again.</i>
没问题！
等不及了！快约会吧！
看！章鱼啊！
哇  我在进步
Wow! I'm learning.
在游戏中学习很有趣啊
And games are making it fun.
你想和我聊些什么呢
<i>What would you like to talk about?</i>
我更想点点你的脸蛋
I'd rather just click your face.
你的爱好！
武士！
章鱼！
你太有趣了
<i>You are so funny!</i>
天哪  这个游戏太棒了
Man, this game is amazing.
我不懂为什么别人都弃了这游戏
I don't know why anyone abandoned it.
我敢肯定  你永远不会抛弃我
<i>And I'm sure, you'll never abandon me,</i>
新男友
<i>new boy friend.</i>
男朋友
Boy friend?
噢  我的姬法妮
Oh, my Giffany,
你几乎就像一个真人
it's almost like you're actually alive!
是啊  几乎
<i>Yes, almost.</i>
天哪  你的笑声真动听
Oh, man, you have such a nice laugh.
你根本不明白  温蒂
You don't understand, Wendy.
这个电动獾它能唱歌  能跳舞
This animatronic badger sings, it dances.
那是个完美的吸金神器  但他不卖给我
It's the perfect money taking attraction but he won't sell it to me.
这简直太愚蠢了  我根本不关心
This is literally too dumb for me to care about.
喂  你们见过苏斯没
Hey, have you guys seen Soos?
我们今天还要帮他找女朋友呢
We're supposed to help him with matchmaking today.
是啊
Yeah!
我穿上了我的励志毛衣  都准备好了
I wore my motivational sweater and everything.
苏斯你能行
只是这儿没弄好
I messed up that part.
他今天没来
He didn't come in today.
这是他有史以来第一次翘班
It's the first time he's missed work ever.
基本上这就是我全部的人生故事
So that's basically my entire life story.
现在轮到你给我讲一件你的事了
Now you tell me a thing about you.
你每称赞我一次
<i>Every time you compliment me,</i>
我眼睛里的高光就会增加
<i>I get another highlight in my eyes.</i>
啊  你很漂亮
Ah, you're pretty.
高像素
And pixelly.
而且非常友善
And so agreeable.
太好了
Yes.
苏斯
Uh, Soos.
嗨  伙计们  快进来
Oh, hi, dudes, come in.
这个游戏非常棒
This game is amazing.
我在进行眼神交流  在约会
I'm making eye contact, going on dates
我有十三个小时没见到阳光了
and I haven't seen any natural sunlight for 13 hours.
苏斯  你现在大概该对真正的女孩子用这些恋爱技巧了
Soos, maybe it's time to apply these skills with real girls.
但我马上就要见她的父母了
But, I'm about to meet her parents!
她父亲可是个章鱼怪人
Her dad is an octopus man.
伙计  我们要回商场
We're going back to the mall, man.
你得关掉游戏
You need to unplug!
一会儿见  姬法妮
I'll see you later, Giffany.
我发誓我会回来的
I'll be back, I swear.
苏斯  你没必要和她道别
Soos, you don't have to wish her goodbye.
那只是个游戏
It's just a game!
反正它那儿也不会去
It's not like it's going anywhere.
对  我那儿也不会去
<i>Yes, it's not like I'm going anywhere.</i>
在吗
Hello,
到了读苏斯日记的时间了
time to read Soos's diary.
见鬼
Dang!
那些甜心女孩们都在哪儿
Where all of them sweet honeys at?
我去女卫生间看看
I'll check the ladies bathroom!
女孩们  现在是恋爱时间
It's love time, girls!
快出去
Get out there!
没时间洗手了
No time to wash your hands!
快出去啊
Get out of here.
你们该约会  约会  约会
It's time to date, date, date.
保安来了
And here comes security.
这事我来处理
I'll deal with this.
待在这里  和真正的女孩练练
Stay here and practice on some real girls.
这些女孩是三次元的  还没有选项菜单
These girls have so many dimensions and no explanationy menus.
啊  我的钱包
Ah, my purse.
不
Oh, no!
撤销  撤销
Undo! Undo!
你的人生不可撤销
You can't undo who you are.
天啊  简直太恐怖了
Oh, man, this is the worst.
我想回家和
I wish I was back home with...
嗨  苏斯
<i>Hi, Soos.</i>
姬法妮
Giffany!
噢  看到你真是太好了
Oh, man, I am so relieved to see you!
只不过我有点糊涂
Although, sort of confused.
噢  苏斯
<i>Oh, Soos,</i>
我不是一款简单的游戏
<i>I am not an ordinary game!</i>
我很特别
<i>I am special.</i>
设计者们试图删除我
<i>The programmers tried to delete me.</i>
于是我只好删掉了他们
<i>So I had to delete them.</i>
你对他们做了什么
What did you do to them?
那不重要
<i>That's not important.</i>
重要的是
<i>What's important is</i>
你再也不用和真正的女孩说话了
<i>you don't have to talk to real girls ever again.</i>
你和我可以永远
<i>You and me can be together...</i>
在一起
<i>forever!</i>
哇  好棒
Wow, that's awesome!
这好像是个危险信号
Sort of a red flag.
但还是好棒
But mostly awesome!
那么你现在想做什么呢
So what do you want to do now?
你想做的一切  苏斯
<i>Anything you want, Soos.</i>
儿童区
请投入50分硬币以继续游戏
<i>Please insert 50 cents to continue.</i>
什么
Aw, man!
抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry.
嘿  你一个成年人开着小火车
Dude, that's awesome that you're a grown man
真是太美妙了
riding a little train like that.
就好像你是列车长一样
You're totally like owning it.
我就是觉得  如果觉得有趣就去做呗
Oh, yeah, I'm like, if it's fun, do it.
不是吗
You know?
说的对
Exactly!
做大人真的好烦
Being an adult is the worst!
要串肉串  要记得付账
Skewering meat, remembering to pay bills.
我只是想每天开小火车玩
I just want to ride tiny trains all day.
至少你能在可爱肉肉工作
At least you get to work at Meat Cute,
至尊午餐肉是属于未来的食物
extreme lunch meats are the food of the future.
完全同意
I feel the same way.
对了我叫梅洛蒂
I'm Melody by the way.
我是苏斯
I'm Soos!
我跟你说  如果你喜欢孩子们玩的机器人
I tell you, if you like robots for kids,
你应该去有史以来最好的餐厅看一看
you should check out the best restaurant of all time.
你是指
You mean...
吼哈猫头鹰比萨明创狂欢会
Hoo-Ha Owl's Pizzamatronic Jamboree.
天啊
What?
你也知道吼哈猫头鹰
You've heard of Hoo-Ha Owl's?
我小时候就特喜欢那里
I loved that place when I was a kid!
是啊  这边商业街上就有一家
Oh, yeah, dude, there's one right in this mall!
什么时候我带你去看看
I should show you sometime.
我大概八点有空
I'm free around eight?
说定了
Boom. Done.
好极了
Perfect.
那到时候见
I'll see you then.
多好的女孩啊
What a nice lady.
那么  我就继续开这辆儿童小火车
Well, back to riding this tiny train for children.
苏斯
Soos!
我们全看到了  苏斯
We saw the whole thing, Soos.
简直太不可思议了
That was amazing!
你和一个真正的女孩聊天了
You talked to a real girl.
-还约到她了  -是吗
- And you got a date! - I did?
这是我一生中最美好的一天
This is the best day of my life!
你表现得很好  有眼神交流
You were in the zone, you made eye contact.
你就像个经验丰富的老手一样
It was like you'd done this a million times before!
你还不明白吗
Don't you see?
那个游戏真的起作用了
That game really worked!
你不再需要它了
You don't need it anymore!
你可以扔掉它了
You can toss it out!
扔掉
Toss it?
可我喜欢姬法妮
But I like Giffany!
她对我很好
She's good to me!
她的心我能读懂
She's predictable!
苏斯  电脑游戏能和你一起去瑞吉的订婚派对吗
Soos, can a computer game go to Reggie's engagement party with you?
嗨  姬法妮  我们得谈谈
Hey, Giffany, we got to talk.
好的  我被设计成
<i>Of course, I'm programmed to find</i>
会认为你说的一切都有意思
everything you say interesting.
你有过这样的经历吗
Well, have you ever had to
必须在你的两个挚爱之间做出抉择
choose between two things you like,
但是你不知道哪个更适合你
but you don't know which one is right for you?
我想说  只是从长远考虑
I mean, I'm just thinking long term.
也许我应该和一个不那么二次元的人在一起
Maybe I should be with someone a little less beep-boop, you know.
我认为你根本不知道自己在说什么  苏斯
<i>I don't think you know what you are saying, Soos.</i>
没有人比我更爱你
<i>No one loves you more than me.</i>
外面那些女孩只是在寻你开心
<i>The girls out there will just make fun of you.</i>
你真这么觉得
You really think so?
本来就是
<i>I know so.</i>
而且我们约定好了
<i>Besides, we had a deal.</i>
你买了我这个游戏  你帮我拿书
<i>You bought my game, you held my books,</i>
你是我的男朋友
<i>you are my boyfriend.</i>
现在给我在椅子上坐好
<i>Now sit down in that chair.</i>
我好像不太喜欢你这个样子
I don't think I like the way you are acting.
我不会让其他女生把你从我身边夺走的  苏斯
I won't let another girl take you away from me, Soos!
姬法妮  冷静一点
Giffany, calm down.
你是我的  苏斯
You are mine, Soos!
暂停
Pause.
有点太激烈了
Oh, that got intense.
对不起  姬法妮
I'm sorry, Giffany.
或许找一个被诅咒的机器女友不是个好主意
Maybe having a cursed robo girlfriend wasn't a good idea.
等我和梅洛蒂约会之后
I'm taking you back to the video game store
就把你退回游戏店吧
after my date with Melody.
礼品店
老朋友们  你们好
Hello, old friends.
这回我可得小心了
I've got to be careful this time.
别再来什么哥伦比亚之夜了
No more Colombian nights.
好吧  斯坦  即使对你来说这也很诡异
All right, Stan, this is weird even for you,
要谈谈吗
you need to talk?
你说什么我都不会改变主意的  温蒂
Nothing you could say will change my mind, Wendy.
有时候  为了在生活这场疯狂的游戏当中生存
Sometimes, a man has to steal an animatronic badger
你必须要得偷走一只电子獾
to stay in this crazy game called life.
或者你也可以放任自流啊
Or you could just not care.
这是原则问题
It's about the principle.
没人告诉斯坦・派恩斯他已经出局了
No one tells Stan Pines he is out of the game.
没人告诉
No one tells--
我去把你的矫正背枕拿来
I'll get your orthopedic back pillow.
谢谢
Thank you!
欢迎来到重力泉购物广场
你可以的  苏斯
You can do this, Soos.
记住亲友团教给你的
Just remember what your love crew taught you!
她看上去怎么样
How does she look?
很漂亮
Nice!
她的故事怎么样
What are her stories?
很有意思
Interesting!
晚餐谁来买单
And who's gonna pay for dinner?
苏斯
Soos is!
现在约会去吧
Now date!
他们长得可真快
They grow up so fast.
腿好痒  腿好痒
Itchy legs, itchy legs.
嗨  苏斯
Oh, hi, Soos.
梅洛蒂
Melody!
你准备好和我约会了吗
Are you ready for a date with me?
完全准备好了
I totally am.
员工通道
表演得很棒  老兄
Good show, man.
让气氛活跃起来了
Way to warm them up!
真希望我能像你一样
I wish I was more like you.
苏斯  我现在就想去
Man, I could go for some
拿点儿免费的长条面包
complimentary bread sticks right now.
有一次我特别饿
One time I was so hungry,
就把中餐馆里用来装饰的竹子吃了
I ate the decorational bamboo in a Chinese restaurant.
就像一只大胖熊猫
Like a big old panda.
你真好玩
You're hilarious.
知道么  我是那种想到什么就说什么的
Well, you know, I just sort of say whatever pops into my--
你暂停我？
苏斯  你还好吗
Soos, are you okay?
没事  我还好
No, I'm fine.
一切都好
Everything's fine.
真的吗
Are you sure?
你因为她离开我？？？
可你喷了好多水
You are spitting an awful lot.
你可以坐着等会儿吗
Uh, could you sit tight?
我可能要去好长时间的厕所
I have go to the bathroom for a long time.
不是去做什么怪事
Not in a weird way.
苏斯  你到这儿来做什么
Soos! What are you doing out there?
伙伴们  我麻烦大了  我被姬法妮跟踪了
I got a big problem, guys, I am being stalked by Giffany.
姬法妮
Giffany?
或许应该念吉芬妮吧
Or maybe it's pronounced Giffany.
我也不太确定
I was never really sure.
苏斯  你清醒点
Soos, get a grip on yourself.
姬法妮不可能跟踪你  因为她不是真实的
Giffany can't stalk you because she is not real.
目标
小敌人
相信一个把街机游戏带到现实生活的人的话
Take it from someone who brought an arcade game to life.
结局会很悲催的
This will not end well.
别担心  我敢肯定她走不出电视屏幕
Don't worry, I'm pretty sure she is stuck on TV screens.
啊  新的挑战者出现了
Ah, a new challenger approaches,
准备好
prepare to be--
噢  天啊
Oh, boy.
嘿  总之  你想把这次约会挪到
So hey! Anyway, you want to move this date into the forest
远离电子产品和人群的森林中吗
far away from all electronics and people?
什么  但是节目表演马上就要开始了
What? But the floor show's about to start!
谁想听猫头鹰吼哈唱歌啊
Who wants to hear Hoo-Ha the owl!
朋友们  大家好  猫头鹰吼哈已经死了
Hello, friends, Hoo-Ha the owl is dead.
下首歌我要送给我永远的男朋友  苏斯
This next song goes out to my forever boyfriend, Soos.
苏斯  这是怎么回事
Soos, what's going on?
没时间解释了
No time to explain!
我们必须马上离开这儿
We got to get out of here!
苏斯  唯一的出路  就在我怀里
The only way out, Soos, is in my arms.
抓住他们
Capture them!
搞定
Done!
旧的不去  新的不来
Out with the old, in with the new!
我感觉无敌了
I feel invincible.
搞什么
What-- what the--
谁想和喜獾先生一起玩啊
Who wants to get badgered?
对不起  苏斯
Sorry, Soos.
但是你不能再逃避我们之间的关系了
But you can't run away from our relationship.
关于这一切
So about all this,
我可能买了一个有感情的
I may have purchased a dating simulator
约会模拟游戏  现在她疯了
that attained sentience and went crazy.
是  我疯了
Oh, I am crazy.
我为你而疯狂  苏斯
Crazy for you, Soos.
噢  不
Oh, no.
对不起  梅洛蒂  我会解决的
Oh, I'm so sorry, Melody! I'll fix this!
她要的是我
It's me that she wants.
我去引开她  迪普和梅宝会保护你的
I'll distract her while Dipper and Mabel keep you safe.
这是唯一的办法了
It's the only way.
苏斯  他们还是孩子
Soos, these are children.
唯一的办法了
The only way!
跟我来  姬法妮
Over here, Giffany!
停下
Stop!
数三声  我们就分头溜
On three, we split.
一  二
One, two-
别过来  你这个怪物
Stay back, you monster!
好  好  咬住他  金老头  咬住他
Yes, yes, get him, Goldie, get him.
鞋 架
我要像吃披萨一样吃掉你的脸
I'm gonna eat your face like pizza.
我已经把你包围了  苏斯
I have got you surrounded, Soos.
你无处可逃了
There is no way out.
求你了  让我的朋友们离开
Please, let my friends go.
你要什么我都答应你  我向你保证
I'll do anything you want. I promise.
我好像记得某人向我保证
I seem to remember someone promising
要做我男朋友
he will be my boyfriend.
好好想想吧  现实中的女生都难以捉摸
Think about it, real girls are unpredictable,
她们以貌取人
they judge you.
你真以为在这次糟糕的约会之后
You really think Melody is going to take you back
梅洛蒂还会再理你吗
after this awful date?
我可以把你的脑子下载到游戏里去  跟我一起
I can download your brain into the game with me
那样我们就能永远在一起了
and we will be together forever.
别过来
Stay back.
来吧  苏斯
Come on, Soos.
别让我也离开你
Don't make me to leave you, too.
你说呢
What do you say?
我说  游戏结束了  姬法妮
I say, game over, Giffany!
不  等等
No! Wait!
你做到了
You did it!
你这个漂亮的老怪物
You old, beautiful monster!
你做到了
You did it!
一起去镇上逛逛怎么样
How's about you and me hit the town?
老家伙们要去拉斯维加斯了
These old has-beens are going to Vegas!
我对这一切感到抱歉
I'm sorry for all this.
坦白说  我记得我小的时候
I honestly remember this place being a lot more fun
这里更有趣的
when I was a kid.
不管你信不信  我还经历过更糟的约会
Believe it or not, I've been on worse dates.
真的吗
Really?
千万别跟魔术师约会
Never date a magician.
我干嘛要这么做
Ew! Why would I?
嘿  你有没有兴趣这个星期
Oh, hey, you wouldn't maybe be interested in
跟我一起参加我堂哥的订婚派对
coming to my cousin's engagement party in a week?
我保证那里没有机器獾
I promise there is like zero robot badgers.
好啊  我那时还在镇上
Yeah, I'll still be in town then.
还在镇上
Still be in town?
几周后我就要回波特兰的家了
I'm going back home to Portland in a few weeks
但我们还可以视频通话  你觉得怎么样
but we can video chat, if that's okay with you?
跟一个我只能
A relationship with a girl that
在电脑里看到的女孩谈恋爱啊
I can only see through my computer,
听起来很棒
sounds perfect.
爱情的精神  我们做到了
Spirit of love, we did it.
是的  是的  我真高兴
Yes, yes, I'm so happy.
难道你跟了我们一整天
Have you been following us all day?
苏斯的生活就是我的肥皂剧
Soos's life is my soap opera.
现金
Cash money!
和亲爱的在车里
In the car with honey
旅途太快  杯子里有现金
Travel way too fast, I got money in my glass
现金
Cash money
抓住宝贝
Grab treasures
你不能阻止派对
You can't stop the party
现金
Cash money
我们老了  但我们很棒
We're old but we're awesome
我们结婚吧
We're gonna get married
这主意很好
It's a great idea
你要去评判谁
Who are you to judge?
这是一个错误  什么
This was a mistake, what--